Never tell them the odds.
Fanboys is a adventure, comedy, crime film directed by Kyle Newman.
In 1999, Star Wars fanatics take a cross-country trip to George Lucas' Skywalker Ranch so
their dying friend can see a screening of The Phantom Menace before its release.
Eric, played by Sam Huntington.
Windows, played by Jay Baruchel.
Hutch, played by Dan Fogler.
Zoe, played by Kristen Bell.
Linus, played by Christopher Rodriguez Marquette.
Chaz, played by David Denman.
Fanboys is a 2009 American comedy film directed by Kyle Newman, and starring Dan
Fogler, Jay Baruchel, Sam Huntington, Chris Marquette, and Kristen Bell.
The story follows a group of Star Wars fans who head on a road trip to Skywalker Ranch to steal a
rough cut of Star Wars: Episode I – The Phantom Menace (1999) for their dying friend.
The Weinstein Company released it in the United States on February 6, 2009.
Metacritic assessed the critical reception as "mixed".
Rotten Tomatoes, another aggregator, said it received negative reviews
and called it "undercooked [and] sporadically funny".
The film explores themes of fan, road trip, rivalry, fan culture, urination.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.